A Guide to the Thomas Wolfe Collection
University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library, #6348-f
Thomas Wolfe Collection
University of Virginia. Library. Special Collections Dept. Alderman Library University of Virginia Charlottesville, Virginia 22903 USA
6348-f
ca. 28 items
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Deposit 1971 Sep 29
Item Listing
- Photographs
  - Photo of ALS, Thomas Wolfe to Julia Wolfe, 1909 Jun 19; Photo
    [Tells her that he has been promoted to the 4th grade, as has his brother Fred Wolfe; speaks about school picnic at Overlook Park; advises her to come home soon as the summer crowd has begun to come in.]
  - Julia Wolfe, standing, ca. 1884; Photo
  - William Oliver Wolfe, standing, Photo
  - Thomas Wolfe, seated, 1906; Photo
  - Thomas Wolfe, standing with foot on a chair, taken at the University of North Carolina, 1916; Photo
  - Julia Wolfe, seated on porch of Old Kentucky Home, Asheville, North Carolina, n. d.; Photo
  - Julia Wolfe, seated, Asheville, North Carolina, n. d.; Photo
  - Julia Wolfe, standing, Asheville, North Carolina, Photo
  - Julia Wolfe, looking at photo of Thomas Wolfe at age 6, n. d.; Photo
  - Wolfe family, 7 members, on porch, [1903]; Photo
  - Wolfe family, 5 members, in front of "Old Kentucky Home", 1906; Photo
  - William Oliver Wolfe, in front of his monument company, 1888; Photo
  - Wolfe family, 15 members, on porch, 1918; Photo
  - Monument of an angel carved by William Oliver Wolfe, n. d.; Photo
  - Monument of an angel carved by William Oliver Wolfe, n. d.; Photo
  - Julia Wolfe, at grave of Thomas Wolfe, Asheville, North Carolina, n. d.; Photo
  - Oversized photo of a boy on a shadowy street, [ Asheville, North Carolina], n. d.; Photo
  - Oversized photo of an old man seated, reading, n. d.; Photo
  - Oversized photo, [Former house of Wolfe family] with three women; Julia Wolfe standing on lawn, Photo
  - Oversized photo, " The Virginian" boarding house, with a group of 5 women, n. d.; Photo
  - Oversized photo, square in [ Asheville, North Carolina], n. d.; Photo
- Miscellaneous
  - Thomas Wolfe, 40 Verandah Terrace, Brooklyn, New York, to James Southall Wilson, Esq., The Virginia Quarterly Review, University of Virginia, 1931 Sep 6; Envelope